https://www.transpack.co.uk/protecting-your-privacy/

£0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Menu
BoxesPostal / Mailing Boxes & TubesPIP BoxesBook PacksPostal TubesCardboard BoxesWardrobe Moving BoxesBook & CD BoxesSingle Wall CartonsBrown Double Wall CartonsSelf-Locking White BoxesSelf-Locking Brown BoxesDisplay/FoodSealfresh Food ContainersCrystal Clear Presentation BoxesLidded Distribution BoxesBagsPolythene BagsClear Polythene Bags100% Recycled BagsNewBlack Poly BagsBiodegradable Grip Seal BagsNewResealable Plastic BagsSchool CarriersMattress Packaging Bags & Covers for Sofa Storage Bin Liners & Waste SacksPlain Carrier Bags - including BiodegradableCellophane BagsArtwork / Photo BagsClear Greeting Card BagsGusseted Cellophane Gift BagsBlock Bottom Cellophane BagsDisplay Bags - Silver Card BaseDisplay Bags - Patterned Silver Card BaseWindow BagsSOS Cellophane Bags With Side GussetsSOS Cellophane Bags With Side Gussets And Silver Card BaseEuroslot Header BagsSmall Clear Multipurpose Gift BagsCone Cellophane Display BagsAccessoriesCompostable BagsCompostable and Biodegradable Greeting Card BagsCompostable & Biodegradable Clear Bags with GussetsCompostable Block Bottom BagsCompostable Block Bottom SOS Bags with Side GussetsCompostable Packing BagsSelf Seal Garment BagsGarment Bags without HookGarment Bags with HookPaper BagsColoured Kraft Paper Carrier BagsKraft Bottle BagsEconomy Paper Carrier Bags with Flat HandlesNewPostal and Mailing BagsMailing BagsJiffy BagsBubble BagsEco-friendly Protective Mailing EnvelopesSchool Bags and Filing BagsSchool CarriersZip Wallets (Supazips)Resealable BagsTissueTissue Paper - WhiteColoured Tissue PaperTissue Paper - Metallic Gold, Silver & CopperPatterned Tissue PaperChristmas Tissue PaperProtectiveHand Sanitiser & Face MasksBubble WrapAnti-static Small BubbleJiffy Large Bubble WrapJiffy Small Bubble WrapBubble BagsSelf Seal Bubble BagsAnti-static Self Seal Bubble BagsPolyethylene FoamJiffy BagsJiffy Airkraft BagsJiffy Padded BagsAir Cushion MachinesPaper Cushioning System - Void FillNewLoose fillGeami Wrapak
- Paper WrappingCentre Folded PVC Shrink FilmMattress & Sofa Storage BagsPure Kraft Paper RollsCapesCorrugated Cardboard RollsEdge and Corner ProtectorsGift & DisplayCellophane Gift
BagsArtwork / Photo BagsGreetings Card BagsEuroslot Header BagsGusseted Cellophane BagsDisplay Bags - Silver Card BaseBlock Bottom Cellophane BagsSmall Clear Gift BagsDisplay Bags - Patterned Silver Card BaseWindow BagsClear Cone Cellophane Sweet & Display BagsAccessoriesSelf Seal Garment BagsTissue PaperTissue Paper - WhiteColoured Tissue PaperTissue Paper - Metallic Gold & SilverBespoke Tissue PaperCellophane WrapRibbonMetallic Elastic CordBakers Twine & Jute RopeCurling RibbonOrganza RibbonSatin RibbonPatterned RibbonStriped RibbonWedding RibbonPolka Dot RibbonVintage RibbonBaby RibbonThank You Ribbon & MoreChristmas RibbonPaper Raffia RibbonCello TubingHamper PackagingCrystal Clear Presentation BoxesWhite Greetings Card EnvelopesPure Kraft Paper RollsColoured Kraft Wrapping PaperAccessoriesPostalPostage BagsClear Mailing Bags Available In A3, A4 & A5 Opaque Mailing BagsBubble BagsBespoke Postage BagsCompostable Mailing BagsPostal BoxesBook PacksLarge Letter BoxesPIP BoxesPostal TubesSelf Locking White BoxesSelf Locking Brown BoxesDocument EnvelopesPlain Paper EnvelopesJiffy BagsJiffy Airkraft BagsJiffy Padded BagsEcolopes - Protective Postal EnvelopesNewPolythenePoly BagsPolythene Clear Plastic BagsColoured Polythene BagsResealable BagsSchool CarriersMattress & Sofa Storage BagsCarrier BagsPolythene Layflat TubingClear Medium Duty Layflat TubingClear Heavy Duty Layflat TubingColoured Heavy Duty Layflat TubingUltra Heavy Duty (1000g) Layflat TubingBlack Heavy DutyPolythene SheetingColoured Polythene SheetingCentre Folded Polythene Sheeting 6ft wideCentre Folded Polythene Sheeting 12ft wideSpa Body WrapCentre Folded PVC Shrink FilmHeat SealersCapesPallet WrapDispenser SystemsPallet & Bundling Stretch FilmPP Strapping & Accessories 12mmStaplersStrapping MachinesSteel StrappingEco FriendlyBagsCompostable Greeting Card BagsCompostable Clear Gusseted BagsCompostable Packing BagsCompostable Block Bottom BagsBiodegradable Grip Seal BagsBiodegradable Carrier Bags100% Recycled Clear BagsRecycled Kraft Paper Carrier BagsGift & Display PostalProtectiveTapesPlain Packaging TapesColoured Packaging TapesWarehousePallet WrapCardboard CartonsBrown Single and Double Wall CartonsWhite Single and Double Wall CartonsJiffy Bubble WrapJiffy Small Bubble WrapJiffy Large Bubble WrapHeat SealersStrapping & Strapping MachinesPP Strapping & AccessoriesSteel StrappingStrapping MachinesAir Cushion MachinesNewPaper Cushioning System - Void FillPacking TapeCentre folded PVC shrinkfilm and Shrink sytemsPallet ProtectionEquipmentAccessoriesCustomBespoke Layflat TubingCustom Tissue PaperPrinted Packing TapeCustom Polythene BagsBespoke Gripseal Bags or Seal Again BagsCustom BoxesCustom Carrier BagsMade to Measure Garment BagsBespoke Bags for Artwork and PhotosPrinted PIP BoxesCustom Cellophane WrapCustom Cellophane Sheets & SleevesCustom Cellophane TubingCellophane Gift Bags, Artwork Bags & Greeting Card BagsCustom Paper BagsCustom Mailing BagsCustom Postal BoxesBespoke Labels & Stickers
COVID-19  We are experiencing extremely high demand at the moment. We are doing our best to despatch every order which is received before 3pm the same day, but unfortunately this cannot be guaranteed.
DPD are not currently offering a guaranteed next day delivery service.
Christmas Hours - We will be closed 23rd Dec to 4th Jan. Please make sure orders are placed by 3pm on 22nd Dec or preferably earlier to ensure delivery before Christmas. Any orders placed after this will not be despatched until 4th Jan 2021.
Home
/
Protecting your privacy - Transpack Ltd
Protecting your privacy - Transpack Ltd
Transpack Limited
This Privacy Notice explains what types of personal data we may collect about you when you interact with us., how we’ll store that data to keep it safe, and how we will use it. It also explains your rights in relation to that data. Any changes to this policy will be available to see via our website.
Transpack Limited – which we’ll refer to as ‘Transpack’ in this document – is a private Company registered in England No. 3392522
The law on data protection sets out a number of different reasons for which a company may collect and process your personal data, including:
Consent - when you tick a box to confirm you are happy to receive communication from us
Contractual obligations - if you place an order with us, we will need to process your data in order to fulfil your order.
Legal Compliance - if the law requires it we can pass on your data to law enforcement agencies if we suspect fraud or other criminal activities
Legitimate Interest - in specific situations, we require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way which might reasonably be expected as part of running our business eg. Using your purchase history to send you relevant offers
We collect your data:
When you visit our website and use your account to buy products and services.
When you create an account with us.
When you purchase a product or service from our warehouse or by phone but don’t have (or don’t use) an account.
When you engage with us on social media.
When you sign up to My Account, you will be given access to an area on Transpack. This will collect and store all your order history allowing you to reorder quickly.
When you contact us by any means with queries.
When you ask one of our Staff to email you information about a product or service.
When you comment on or review our products and services.
When you fill in any forms. For example, opening a Trade Account with us.
When you’ve given a third party permission to share with us the information they hold about you.
When our Financial Services suppliers– such as SagePay or Paypal – share information with us about the product you have purchased.
What sort of personal data do we collect?
If you have a web account with us: your name, title, billing/delivery address, orders and receipts, email and telephone number.
For your security, we’ll also keep an encrypted record of your login password – this allows you to log in and see your previous order details.
Details of your interactions with us through our warehouse or office or online
For example, we collect notes from our conversations with you, details of any complaints or comments you make, details of purchases you made, items viewed or added to your basket, wish list choices, voucher redemptions, web pages you visit and how and when you contact us.
Details of your visits to our website, and which site you came from to ours
Information gathered by the use of cookies in your web browser. Learn more about How we use Cookies.
Your comments and product reviews.
Payment card information if you order over the phone. This is then destroyed after the transaction is complete. (Payment via our website is through a secure third party company which means that payment information is not visible to us, and not collected).
To deliver the best possible web experience, we collect technical information about your internet connection and browser as well as the country and telephone code where your computer is located, the web pages viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms you entered.
Your social media username, if you interact with us through those channels, to help us respond to your comments, questions or feedback.
How and why do we use your personal data?
We want to give you the best possible customer experience and to be able to offer you any relevant information regarding new products or special offers. One way to achieve that is to look at your order history, which allows us to only contact you when it is totally relevant.
The data privacy law allows this as part of our legitimate interest in understanding our customers and providing the highest levels of service.
Here’s how we’ll use your personal data and why:
To process any orders that you make by using our website, or over the phone. If we don’t collect your personal data during checkout, we won’t be able to process your order and comply with our legal obligations.
To respond to your queries, refund requests and complaints. Handling the information you sent enables us to respond. We may also keep a record of these to aid any future communication with us and to demonstrate how we communicated with you throughout. We do this on the basis of our contractual obligations to you, our legal obligations and our legitimate interests in providing you with the best service.
To protect our business and your account from fraud and other illegal activities. This includes using your personal data to maintain, update and safeguard your account. We’ll also monitor your browsing activity with us to quickly identify and resolve any problems and protect the integrity of our websites. We’ll do all of this as part of our legitimate interest.
To process payments and to prevent fraudulent transactions. We do this on the basis of our legitimate business interests. This also helps to protect our customers from fraud.
With your consent, we will use your personal data, preferences and details of your transactions to keep you informed by email, web, telephone or post and through customer services about relevant products and services including tailored special offers, discounts and , promotions. Of course, you can opt out of these communications at any time.
To send you communications required by law or which are necessary to inform you about our changes to the services we provide you. For example, product recall notices, and legally required information relating to your orders. These service messages will not include any promotional content and do not require prior consent when sent by email. If we do not use your personal data for these purposes, we would be unable to comply with our legal obligations.
To display the most interesting content to you on our website, we’ll use data we hold about your favourite brands or products and so on. We do so on the basis of your consent to place cookies or similar technology on your device.
To comply with our contractual or legal obligations to share data with law enforcement.
To send you feedback requests to help improve our services. These messages will not include any promotional content and do not require prior consent when sent by email. We have a legitimate interest to do so as this helps make our products or services more relevant to you.
Of course, you are free to opt out of receiving these requests from us at any time by unsubscribing when you receive an email.
How we protect your personal data?
We will treat your data with the utmost care and take all appropriate steps to protect it.
We secure access to all areas of our website using ‘https’ technology.
Access to your personal data is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as payment card information) is secured by SSL encryption. Online payments are only handled by a third party card handling company through a fully encrypted site attached to this one. None of our staff have sight of your card details when you order online.
Who do we share your personal data with?
We sometimes need to share your personal data with trusted third parties. This could be delivery couriers or technicians visiting your premises. We will provide only the information they need to perform the specific services, they may only use your data for those services.
Sharing your data with third parties for their own purposes:
We will only do this in very specific circumstances, for example:
For fraud management, we may share information about fraudulent or potentially fraudulent activity in our premises or systems. This may include sharing data about individuals with law enforcement bodies.
We may also be required to disclose your personal data to the police or other enforcement, regulatory or Government body, in your country of origin or elsewhere, upon a valid request to do so. These requests are assessed on a case-by-case basis and take the privacy of our customers into consideration.
We may, from time to time, expand, reduce or sell the Company and this may involve the transfer of the whole business to new owners. If this happens, your personal data will, where relevant, be transferred to the new owner or controlling party, under the terms of this Privacy Notice.
To help personalise your journey through Transpack’s website we use various third party companies including Google, Facebook and Twitter who will process your personal data as part of their contracts with us.
International orders
If you are based outside the UK and place an order with us, any data collected from you will be processed by our UK office.
Protecting your data outside the EEA
We may transfer personal data that we collect from you to third-party data processors in countries that are outside the EEA. For example, this might be required in order to fulfil your order. If we have to do this we will ensure your data is protected and treated in line with this Privacy Policy.
You have the right to:
Access the personal data we hold about you – there is usually no charge for this
The correction of your personal data when incorrect, out of date or incomplete.
Request that we stop using your personal data for direct marketing (either through specific channels, or all channels).
To change your mind if you have previously given consent to us contacting you for marketing purposes.
To ask for your information, please contact Data Protection Officer, Unit K, Griffin Industrial Park, Brunel Road, Totton. SO40 3SH
or email sales@transpack.co.uk. To ask for your information to be amended, please update your online account, or contact our Customer Services team.
If we haven’t answered your questions
We hope this Privacy Notice has been helpful in setting out the way we handle your personal data and your rights to control it.
If you have any questions that haven’t been answered, please contact our Data Protection Officer who will be pleased to help you:
Email us at sales@transpack.co.uk
Or write to us at Data Protection Officer, Unit K, Griffin Industrial Park, Brunel Road, Totton. SO40 3SH
